我们都算过了
The math is all there.
-那是不可能的  -才不是  是真的!
It's not real. Yes, it is.
你看啊  从科学的角度说
Yeah... uh, look. It is scientifically impossible
一个人想要把一头牛绊倒是绝对不可能的
for a person to tip a cow.
就算是你这种敦实健壮的女汉子也是不可能的
Even you, with your stocky build and lumberjack shoulders, you couldn't do it.
太恶劣了  你们干嘛要把牛推倒?
It's horrible. Why would you push a cow over?
牛是神圣的动物
They're sacred.
你还有脸说
Oh, stop it.
你都吃了几千几万个汉堡了(夹着牛肉饼)
I've seen you eat, like, a million hamburgers.
动物可以既神圣又美味的
Hey, an animal can be both sacred and delicious.
我不骗你们  我真的干过
Look, I'm telling you I've done it, okay?
我清楚地记得那头牛先是站着的
I clearly remember the cow standing up
后来就倒在了地上
and then the cow on its side.
你是喝高了吧?
Were you drunk?
我当时可是16岁的西部牛仔小青年  你觉得呢?
I was 16 in Nebraska. What do you think?
我觉得你才是那个摔倒的
I think you're the one who fell over.
难怪当时天空也是倒着的
That would explain why the sky was also on its side.
Howard  推倒一头牛  你觉得是真的吗?
Howard. Cow tipping: real or not?
我觉得应该是假的
Mmm. I'm gonna say... not.
我是根据在我妈打呼时我想给她翻个身的经历得出的
That's just based on me trying to roll my mom over when she's snoring.
说到我这个大肉球老妈啊
Speaking of that big side of beef,
她邀请你们所有人来她家过感恩节
uh, she's invited all of you to Thanksgiving at her house.
他们告诉我直接拒绝别人的邀请很不礼貌
You know, I've been told that a bald refusal of an invitation is rude
应该给一个客气的借口  所以...
and one must instead offer up a polite excuse, so...
我想去的  但很遗憾  这个主意简直太可怕了
I'd love to go, but, unfortunately, that sounds awful.
别这样嘛  会很好玩的
Come on, it'll be fun.
其实我们想在这儿过节的
Uh, we were actually gonna do it here.
拜托了  Bernadette要带她老爸过来
Please. Bernadette's bringing her dad
因为她妈妈有事出去了
'cause her mom's out of town,
我跟他完全没话讲啊
and I never have anything to say to that guy.
既然你这么说了  我想去的
Oh, since you put it that way, I'd love to go,
但这听起来更可怕了
but that sounds even more awful.
其实不用听Sheldon整天跟我抱怨菜很难吃也挺好的
It'd actually be nice to not hear Sheldon complain about my cooking all day.
容我说一句
Yo... uh, excuse me,
每年你都做一桌难吃的菜
but every year you prepare a terrible meal
每年我都批评你
and every year I criticize it.
我们的这个传统对你来说就一点也不重要吗?
Do our traditions mean nothing to you?
-我想去  -我也想去
-I want to go.  -Yeah, me, too.
我也去  Sheldon你呢?
I'm in. Sheldon?
好吧  我会去的
Ugh, fine, I'll go.
但是如果她做的菜很好吃  感恩节就算毁了
But if her food is delicious, Thanksgiving is ruined,
而且全都是你的错
and it's on you.
Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state
Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait!
The Earth began to cool
The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools
We built the Wall We built the pyramids
Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery
That all started with a big bang
Bang!
The Big Bang Theory 7x09 The Thanksgiving Decoupling Original Air Date on November 21, 2013
我们真的一定要去Wolowitz夫人家吗?
Do we really have to go to Mrs. Wolowitz's house?
当然
We do.
而且我希望你能表现出最好的一面
And I expect you to be on your best behavior.
我现在知道非洲奴隶的心情了
Now I know how the African slaves felt.
从家里被人拖走
Being dragged from their homes
在白人的统治下劳动
to labor under the yoke of the white man.
你真的是要把去Wolowitz妈妈家吃感恩节晚餐
Are you honestly comparing Thanksgiving dinner at Wolowitz's mom's
和人类历史上最大的悲剧之一相提并论吗?
with one of the greatest tragedies in the history of mankind?
嗯
Yes.
Sheldon  不论在哪儿  你都可以过一个开心的感恩节
Sheldon, you can have a nice Thanksgiving anywhere.
我有次就在拉斯维加斯过的
I spent one in Vegas.
真的?
You did?
是啊  我当时还在跟Zack谈恋爱
Yeah, back when I was dating Zack.
比我想的要有意思多了
It was actually more fun than I thought.
赌赌博呀  逛逛那种山寨的婚礼小教堂呀
We gambled, we went to one of those cheesy wedding chapels,
那顿火鸡晚餐真的很棒
we had a really good turkey dinner.
很让人惊喜  因为我们是在脱衣舞夜总会吃的
Which was surprising, since we were at a strip club.
等等  你们去了教堂?
Wait, you went to a chapel?
是呀  怎么了?
Yeah. Why?
我们还办了那种超搞笑的假婚礼
We had one of those silly fake weddings.
Penny...
你知道那是真的结了婚  对吧?
you know those are real, right?
不  才不是
No, they're not.
是真的
Yeah, they are.
不  才不是
No, they're not.
真的是真的
Yeah, they are.
-他说得对  -是真的
-He's right.  -They're real.
但是  看着不像真的啊
But it... didn't seem real.
我来问你一下
Let me ask you a question.
是不是有那么一段时间  拉斯维加斯是躺着的?
At any point, was Las Vegas on its side?
嗨  老爸
Hi, Dad.
嗨  宝贝
Hi, honey.
哇  你给大家都带了啤酒
Oh, you brought beer for everybody.
好吧  是的  这是给大家喝的
Uh, okay, yeah, it's for everybody.
我本来只是想安安静静地在家看球赛的
I really just wanted to have a nice, quiet day at home and watch the game.
在这里也可以安静地看球赛呀
You can have a quiet day and watch the game here.
Howard  这药不管用!
Howard, the medicine's not working!
你才刚吃下去
You just took it.
起码等这药到你的第一个胃再说吧!
At least let it reach your first stomach!
你好呀  Mike
Hey, Mike.
我来帮你拿
Let me help you out, there.
谢谢  亲家母怎么了?
Thanks. What's wrong with your mom?
她的痛风又发作了
Oh, her gout's flaring up.
看来每天一个苹果派不能让医生远离你
Turns out an apple pie a day does not keep the doctor away.
一个小小的脚指头怎么能痛成这样?
How can one little toe hurt so bad?
可能是因为那头小猪(脚指头)正被牲口棚压着呢!
Maybe because that little piggy is being crushed by the barn!
她马上就能安静下来了
She should quiet down soon.
我给她吃了能把一头... 把她放倒的止痛药
I gave her enough pain meds to choke a... well, her.
看来得我们自己来做饭了
I guess we're gonna have to do all the cooking.
我有个更好的注意
I have a better idea.
如果你想全让我来做  你脑子就有问题
If you think you're gonna make me do all this by myself, you're crazy.
我是想全让Raj来做
I was gonna make Raj do it all by himself.
这个主意超棒
Oh, well, that's a great idea.
不堵车  真是一帆风顺呀
No traffic, we're sailing.
是啊
Yes.
我们就好像在船上
Like we're on a ship.
从非洲到美洲
Coming from Africa to America.
Sheldon  这完全不合适
Sheldon, that's completely inappropriate.
你不能一直把你自己和奴隶相比
You can't keep comparing yourself to a slave.
是的  Amy小姐
Yes, Miss Amy.
真是难以相信你居然和那个白痴结婚了
I can't believe you're married to that idiot.
能不能别再说了? 我们这么做只是玩玩而已
Ugh, would you stop? We just did it as a goof.
不管你们是不是认真的  你的确已婚了
Well, a goof or not, you're actually married.
你必须把这件事料理好
You need to get this taken care of.
我会的  为什么你这么大惊小怪的?
I will. Why are you making this such a big deal?
哦哦哦  我是有个理由
Oh, oh, oh, I have a reason.
也许是因为你和Zack结婚了
It could be because you said yes to marrying Zack,
但是每次Leonard求婚时
but every time Leonard's proposed,
他都会得到一个响亮的"不"
he's gotten a resounding no.
是啊  这只是我立刻能想到的理由
Yeah, that's just off the top of my head.
那么我该如何弥补呢?
So how do I undo this?
我希望你能废除这个婚姻
I'm hoping you can get an annulment.
就好像从来没发生过一样
It's just like it never happened.
好极了  那么我该怎么做呢?
Great, well, what do I have to do?
上面说以下这些情况满足的话
It says here you can get an annulment
你就可以废除婚姻了
if any of the following conditions are met.
你是否无法完成夫妻生活?
"Were you unable to consummate the marriage?"
哈哈  Penny? 下一条
Penny? Next.
是否有任何欺骗  重婚
"Is there any evidence of fraud, bigamy,
或者理解匮乏?
want of understanding?"
理解匮乏?
"Want of understanding?"
那是什么意思?
What does that even mean?
叮叮叮  我们找到赢家了
Ding, ding, ding. We have a winner.
感谢今天能来
Thanks for saving the day.
啊  没关系
Ah, no problem.
如果今天没有印度人给你们做菜的话
It wouldn't be Thanksgiving
今天就不能算得上感恩节了
without an Indian providing the food.
唔  你妈妈把油放哪了?
Uh, now, where does your mom keep the Crisco?
唔  我不知道
Um, I don't know.
大概在她脸上的一团肉里吧
Probably in a wad in her cheek.
我在这里帮Raj  你为啥不去陪陪我爸爸呢?
I'll help Raj in here. Why don't you go keep my dad company?
他不想我呆在那  我是那个睡了他女儿的
Oh, he doesn't want me in there. I'm the creepy little guy
变态的小矮子
who has sex with his daughter.
-别傻了  他爱你的  -是吗?
-Don't be silly, he loves you. -Does he?
-好吧  他很关心你  -真的吗?
-Okay, he cares about you a lot. -Really?
我总是为你擦屁股  滚粗去
I do crap for you all the time. Get out there.
那么你妻子去亚利桑那州看孙子了?
So your wife's in Arizona with the grandkids?
嗯
Uh-huh.
知道吗  我老妈曾经去过亚利桑那
You know, my mom's been to... Arizona.
她曾骑驴到大峡谷里
She rode one of those mules down in the Grand Canyon.
简而言之  他们不得不把驴杀了
Long story short, they had to shoot it.
因为她太胖
'Cause she's so fat.
我去开门  你接着笑
I'll get the door while you finish laughing.
大家好
Hey, guys.
感恩节快乐
Happy Thanksgiving.
闻起来真不错
It smells wonderful.
是不是有人在厨房里干苦力呢?
Is anyone slaving away in the kitchen?
-因为我也知道...  -Sheldon
-Because I, too, know... -Sheldon.
给你  谢谢你的邀请
Here. Thank you for having us.
你怎么了?
What's with you?
哦  她生我的气
Oh, she's mad at me
因为她发现她已经和Zack结婚了
because she just found out she's married to Zack.
真的?
Really?
你以前约会的那个二货?
That dumb-ass she used to date?
太搞笑了
That's hysterical.
不敢相信我在车里打开酒时居然会觉得抱歉
I can't believe I felt bad for opening this in the car.
需要帮助吗?
You need any help?
嗯  你能把那个肉汁壶拿过来吗?
Uh, yeah, can you, uh, reach that, uh, gravy boat up there?
-当然  -好的
-Uh, sure. -Great.
总算有人能够得着了
That makes one of you.
好的  我们要做很多事但是时间却不够了
Okay, we have a lot to do and not much time to do it.
Bernadette你负责玉米,肉汁和红薯
Bernadette, you're on corn, gravy and yam detail.
Amy  你负责面包卷,小红莓
Amy, you're on rolls, cranberries
并且确定Bernadette不再偷吃棉花糖
and making sure Bernadette stays away from the marshmallows.
没错  我看到了
That's right, I see you.
好的  如果有任何问题
Okay, if you have any questions,
我就在这里忙着给我的烤火鸡涂汁
I'll be over here basting my ass off.
专注是最关键的
Focus is key.
你们知不知道三年前Penny和Zack已经结婚了
Did you guys know Penny married Zack three years ago?
-什么?  -什..?
-What? -Wha...?
你打过橄榄球没?
You ever play football?
大学时打过
A little in college.
你呢?
You?
没有
No.
但是我在走廊被拦截摔倒过一次
But I did get tackled in the hallway once.
整个学校都沸腾了
The whole school cheered.
嗨  我找到了你和Zack需要填写的
Hey, I found the, uh, court papers
法律文件了
that you and Zack need to fill out.
当我们回家的时候我就把它打印出来  好的
I'll print them when we get home. Fine.
然后我们就当他完全没发生过
And we can just put this whole thing behind us.
够了没?
Are you done?
-怎么了?  -听着  我知道了  我犯了错
-What? -Look, I get it, I screwed up.
我们接下来的一整天都要一直谈论这个吗?
Is this all we're gonna talk about the rest of the day?
干啥冲我发火?
Why are you mad at me?
你才是那个做傻事的人
You're the one that did the stupid thing.
-我只是在想解决办法  -噢!
-I'm just trying to fix it. -Ugh!
我要去透透气
I need some air.
Penny
Well... Penny.
我不知道和女人相处的第一准则是什么
Now, I don't know the first thing about women,
但是我不会追她的
but I would not follow her.
听这个竹竿的没错
Listen to Stretch.
我怎么成了坏人了?
How am I the bad guy?
她才是和别人结婚的人  我是受害者
She's the one who married someone else. I'm the victim.
听起来Zack才是受害者  你把他老婆睡了
Sounds like Zack's the victim. You're sleeping with his wife.
我已经结婚35年了
I've kept my marriage together for 35 years.
我能在这儿发表点意见吗?
Can I weigh in here?
当然
Sure.
我想看比赛  闭嘴
I'm trying to watch the game. Shut up.
噢!
Oh!
你在那儿首攻怎么会不成功呢?
How do you not make a first down there?
他们过了个五防守阵型
They passed against a nickel defense.
他们应该跑躲避拦截的路线
They should have run it off-tackle.
你怎么知道这个的?
How the hell do you know that?
我爸以前喜欢橄榄球
My father loved football.
他总逼我看
He always made me watch it
没看完之前我不许做作业
before I was allowed to do my homework.
现在你会很乐意知道
PENNY: Well, you'll be happy
我刚刚和Zack通过电话
to know I just spoke to Zack
他说他愿意在法庭文件上签字
and he's willing to sign the court papers.
他就在来的路上了
He's on his way here now.
-等等  你邀请他来这儿了?  -对啊
Wait, you invited him here? Yeah.
我又准备好发表意见了
I'm getting ready to weigh in again.
来这边吧
Come on.
你觉得他们现在该怎么做?
What do you think they ought to do now?
如果是我会做个迅速斜线进攻扔个一个边线
I would throw a quick slant to a wideout,
鉴于防守呈现闪电战局面
given that the defense is showing blitz.
噢  我超爱绝佳闪电战  尤其是有酸奶油的
Oh, I love a good blitz, especially with sour cream.
没听懂吗?
Get it?
因为这听着像"薄饼卷"啊
'Cause it sounds like "blintz."
有人说薄饼卷吗?
MRS. WOLOWITZ: Did someone say "blintz"?!
我就是不明白
I just don't understand
你今天为什么邀请他来
why you invited him here today.
因为你就是咬着不放
Because you wouldn't shut up about it.
我打给他的时候  他没事可做
When I called him, he had nothing to do,
所以我想着...
so I just thought it would...
嘿  我在这儿做饭呢
Hey, guys, I'm trying to cook in here.
噢  对不起  我们会小点声的
Oh, sorry. We'll keep it down.
不不不  大点儿声
No, no, speak up.
我马上要用搅拌机了
I'm about to use the blender,
我可不想错过任何事情
and I don't want to miss anything.
好吧  你可能得再做多一人份了
Well, you might have to cook for one more
因为她邀请了Zack来
because she invited Zack.
-神马?!!!  - 噢天啊!
BERNADETTE: What? AMY: Ooh!
啧啧啧
My, my.
剧情如我的肉汁  愈发香浓呢
The plot, like my gravy, thickens.
我不喜欢你母亲的卫生间
I don't care for your mother's bathroom.
没有一个角度可以解决私人问题
There's not an angle to do one's business
而不被一个小丑雕像盯着的
without a clown figurine staring at you.
这就是我坐着的原因
That's why I sit.
对  原因是这个
Yeah, that's why.
你记得那场感恩节时的比赛吗
You remember the Thanksgiving game
达拉斯州下雪的时候
when it snowed in Dallas?
1993年  Leon Lett在最后一秒毁了比赛
1993-- Leon Lett blew the game in the final seconds
然后Dolphins获胜了
and the Dolphins emerged victorious.
而我终于可以做微积分去了
Then I finally got to do my calculus.
我当时气得想一枪射了我的电视
I was so pissed, I wanted to shoot my TV.
我爸也是
So was my dad.
而且他也那么做了
And then he did.
-有人要喝啤酒吗?  -好的
Anyone need a beer? Yeah.
谢谢老天爷
Thank God.
那么  你爸爸还住在德克萨斯州吗?
So, does your dad still live in Texas?
不  他在我14岁时去世了
No. He died when I was 14.
听到这个真难过
I'm sorry to hear that.
当地小酒馆的老板也很难过
So was the man who owned the local liquor store.
他哭了一遍又一遍
He cried and cried.
给
Here you go.
哦谢谢
Oh, thanks.
这么说  如果你父亲在你14岁时过世了
So, if your dad died when you were 14,
你年龄还从未大到可以和他喝啤酒
you were never old enough to have a beer with the man.
是的
No, sir.
他确实试图在我高中毕业时给我一瓶
He did try to give me one for my high school graduation,
但我才11岁  我妈说不行
but I was 11 and my mom said no.
好吧  你来跟我一起喝一罐吧
Well, you're having one with me.
好吧
All right.
敬你的父亲
To your dad.
我也从未和我爸喝过啤酒
I never had a beer with my dad, either.
不好意思  我们在这共度时光呢
Do you mind? We're having a moment here.
难以置信Penny已经嫁给Zack了
I can't believe Penny's married to Zack.
不知道她看上那小子什么了
Wonder what she saw in that guy.
我不知道
I don't know.
他又温柔  又高  又帅
He's sweet, he's tall, handsome.
宽厚的肩膀  漂亮的头发
Broad shoulders, good hair.
嗯  不知道他看上Leonard什么了
Hmm. Wonder what she sees in Leonard.
外面怎么样?
How's it going out there?
Sheldon在和你爸联络感情  我被完全忽视
Sheldon and your dad are bonding and completely ignoring me.
我了解你的感受
I know how you feel.
Sheldon有Roomba自动吸尘器的时候  忽视了我一周
Sheldon ignored me for a week when he got that Roomba vacuum.
我会趁他不注意的时候踢它
I kick it when he's not looking.
他们在干嘛?
What are they doing?
-喝啤酒看橄榄球  -那你怎么不一块儿?
They're drinking beer and watching football. So why don't you do that with them?
他们不想让我一起
They don't want me.
这是什么意思?
What do you mean?
Sheldon说起
Well, Sheldon started talking
他爸爸已经不在了
about how his dad isn't alive anymore,
然后他们就开始祝酒  我也试着
and they were toasting, and I tried
去告诉他们
to tell them about how sad I was
他爸抛弃我时有多难过...
when my dad abandoned...
Zack到了!
AMY: Zack's here!
搅拌肉汁
Stir the gravy.
抱歉  我真的想听你有多难过
Sorry. I really want to hear how sad you are.
我会在五到十分钟后回来
I'll be back in like five, ten minutes.
抱歉她让你在节日里跑一趟
Sorry she made you come over here on a holiday.
没什么  我反正也没在做什么
It's all right. I didn't have anything going on.
再说Penny告诉我  我们结婚了
Plus, Penny told me we're married,
感恩节就是亲人团聚的日子嘛
and Thanksgiving's a time to be with family.
行行
Yeah, okay, great.
那就赶紧签了吧?
Can we just get this over with?
好  你们要在这里... 还有这里签名
Yeah, uh, you guys have to sign here and here.
周一就可以申请废除婚姻
On Monday, we'll file for the annulment,
然后这场"婚姻"就结束了
and this "marriage" will be over.
签好了
Okay.
我还没想好要不要签
I don't know if I want to sign it.
-唔?  -唔~~
-Ooh. Ooh.  -Ooh.
为什么你不想签?
Why won't you sign it?
我只是觉得离婚了  孩子们不好过啊
I just think splitting up can be rough on kids.
我们又没小孩
We don't have any kids.
你确定吗? 因为你也是今天早上
Are you sure? 'Cause you didn't know
才知道我们结婚了
we were married until this morning.
Zack  你听我说
Okay, look, Zack, come on.
你清楚我们俩谁也没以为那是真的啊
You know neither of us thought this was real.
我们的证婚人还是猫王模仿达人啊
I mean, we were married by an Elvis impersonator.
当然是找模仿达人啦
Of course it was an impersonator.
我们哪有钱请猫王本人啊
We could never afford a real Elvis.
你嫁给他  而不嫁我?
You married him instead of me?
有眼光
Good call.
快签
Sign the papers.
等下  你知道吗?
Hang on. You know what?
你一天都因为这事咄咄逼人
You have been a jerk about this all day.
你老是这样... 我每次搞砸什么事
You always do this... whenever I mess up,
你就不遗余力地让我感觉更糟
you're right there to make me feel even worse about it.
才不是呢
That is not true.
是吗  我们明明可以等到周一
Yeah, we could've waited till Monday,
直接签字  这件事就可以结束了啊
signed the papers, this all would have been over.
是你请他过来的
You're the one who invited him here.
又来啦... 又一个推卸到我身上
Oh, there you go again... just another mistake
的错误
you're throwing in my face.
这可不对哦  兄弟
Not cool, bro.
我开始觉得
I'm starting to think
我不喜欢你这样的人和我老婆约会
you're not the kind of guy I want dating my wife.
那个...
Yeah, well,
她很快就不是你老婆了
she's not gonna be your wife for long.
不是吧  你快死了吗?
Oh, no. Are you dying?
快了... 签字吧
I'm about to. Sign the paper.
俗话说得好  媳妇开心  夫复何求
Know what they say: "Happy wife, happy life."
开饭吧
Let's eat.
二  三  八  四  六
Two, three, eight, four, six.
我只能做到这里了  不然就吐了
That's all I can do without throwing up.
你说你要打嗝打出个“派”的时候
That is not what I expected
我可没想到是这样的
when you said you were gonna burp "pie."
是不是有人说要"派"呀?!
Did somebody say "pie"?!
我都说不清以下哪样更恐怖:
I don't know what's scarier:
浴室小丑呢
the bathroom clowns
还是把小丑放在浴室的女人
or the woman that put them there.
我只知道你只能把一个她放到车里去
All I know is you can only fit one of her in a car.
这就是她生出来的那个小丑
And there's the clown that came out of her.
我本来挺不想来的
I really didn't want to come here,
但是这马上就要变成
but this is shaping up to be
多年来我过的最棒的感恩节了
one of the best Thanksgivings I've had in a long time.
我也是
Me, too.
嘿  Howie说你们一整天都在拿他开涮
Hey. Howie says you've been making fun of him all day!
你们俩现在就向他道歉
Now, both of you apologize
现在!
right now!
她好迷你啊
She's so tiny.
她发飙了好有趣哦
It's funny when she's mad.
好了  这位先生
All right, mister, I think you owe
我觉得你欠Howard和Bernadette一个道歉
Howard and Bernadette an apology.
你说得对
Perhaps you're right.
我对我的所作所为感到抱歉
I'm sorry for my behavior.
我喝了点酒
I've had alcohol, and it's caused me
导致我行为不端
to be inappropriate.
-没事  -别放心上
-It's okay.  -Don't worry about it.
谢谢
Thank you.
她是不是很棒?
Ain't she great?
是呀
Mmm.
Sheldon别闹
Sheldon.
那去给我们拿点啤酒来吧
Now, how's about you get us a couple of beers?
再次谢谢你下厨掌勺
Thanks again for cooking.
是呀  每样都很好吃
Yeah, everything was delicious.
要是没两位我最爱的姑娘帮我  我也搞不定
Well, I couldn't have done it without my two favorite girls.
Martha Stewart(富商及专栏作家)和Rachael Ray(电视烹饪女王)
Martha Stewart and Rachael Ray.
Sheldon  我们要不要出去
Hey, Sheldon, what do you say we go outside
去玩玩老猪皮(即:橄榄球)?
and throw around the old pigskin?
这是个犹太家庭
This is a Jewish house.
我觉得不会有猪皮
I don't think they have pigskin.
是不是有人说到"猪皮"啦?
Did someone say "pigskin"?
亲爱的  今天的事我很抱歉
Hey, honey, I'm sorry about today.
我向你保证  下次我结婚的时候
And I promise, next time I get married,
不会再当玩笑了
it won't be a joke.
我会为爱而结婚
It'll be for love.
或者为钱
Or money.
我也很抱歉
I'm sorry, too.
别内疚
Don't be.
都是我的错
It's my fault.
我是个糟糕的丈夫
I was a terrible husband.
我从来没好好陪她
I was never around.
我知道我对你很严格
I know I'm hard on you,
但你还不算是世界上最烂的女婿
but you're not the worst son-in-law in the world.
Mike  这是你对我过说的最感人的话了
Mike, that's the nicest thing you've ever said to me.
是呀是呀  我喝多了
Well, I'm drunk.
我刚刚吐了很多小丑一身
I just vomited on a lot of clowns.